export const chapter = "Chapter - 14: Tense";
export const noOfActivities = 3;

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 1) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Tick the correct option:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "In which tense can you express habitual action or general truths?",
          optionA: "A. Present Continuous Tense",
          optionB: "B. Simple Future Tense",
          optionC: "C. Simple Present Tense",
          correctAnswer: "C. Simple Present Tense",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which tense is used to indicate an action that occurred in the past?",
          optionA: "A. Simple Past Tense",
          optionB: "B. Present Perfect Tense",
          optionC: "C. Future Perfect Continuous Tense",
          correctAnswer: "A. Simple Past Tense",
        },
        {
          question: "What does Present Perfect Tense indicate?",
          optionA: "A. Action going on at present",
          optionB: "B. Action that took place in the past with present impact",
          optionC: "C. Continuous action in the future",
          correctAnswer:
            "B. Action that took place in the past with present impact",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which tense is used to show a completed action before another took place?",
          optionA: "A. Past Perfect Continuous Tense",
          optionB: "B. Future Perfect Tense",
          optionC: "C. Present Perfect Tense",
          correctAnswer: "A. Past Perfect Continuous Tense",
        },
        {
          question: "What does the Future Continuous Tense indicate?",
          optionA: "A. Action that will take place in the future and continue",
          optionB: "B. Action that occurred in the past",
          optionC: "C. Action that is happening at the present time",
          correctAnswer:
            "A. Action that will take place in the future and continue",
        },
        {
          question: "When is the Present Perfect Continuous Tense used?",
          optionA: "A. Indicate an action in the past",
          optionB: "B. Express future actions",
          optionC: "C. Action began in the past and is still continuing",
          correctAnswer: "C. Action began in the past and is still continuing",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Which tense refers to an action that will be finished by a certain time in the future or before another event occurs in the future?",
          optionA: "A. Future Perfect Continuous Tense",
          optionB: "B. Past Perfect Tense",
          optionC: "C. Future Perfect Tense",
          correctAnswer: "C. Future Perfect Tense",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In which tense can you describe what happens in a film or television show, or what is described in a book?",
          optionA: "A. Simple Past Tense",
          optionB: "B. Simple Present Tense",
          optionC: "C. Present Continuous Tense",
          correctAnswer: "B. Simple Present Tense",
        },
        {
          question: "When is the Past Continuous Tense used?",
          optionA:
            "A. To indicate an action that continued over a period of time in the past",
          optionB: "B. To express future actions",
          optionC:
            "C. To indicate an action that will take place in the future and continue",
          correctAnswer:
            "A. To indicate an action that continued over a period of time in the past",
        },
        {
          question: "What does the Future Perfect Continuous Tense indicate?",
          optionA: "A. Continuous action in the future",
          optionB: "B. Completed action before another took place",
          optionC:
            "C. Action that will be finished by a certain time in the future",
          correctAnswer: "A. Continuous action in the future",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 2) {
  activityData = {
    activity: "Fill in the blanks:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "The Simple Present or Present Indefinite Tense expresses habitual action or general truths. For example, 'I attend school daily. Old people love to give __________.'",
          optionA: "A) Advice",
          optionB: "B) Money",
          optionC: "C) Gifts",
          correctAnswer: "A) Advice",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Simple Past or Past Indefinite Tense is used to indicate an action that occurred in the past. For instance, 'She applied for the post of a receptionist. The maid cleaned the room __________.'",
          optionA: "A) Swiftly",
          optionB: "B) Well",
          optionC: "C) Haphazardly",
          correctAnswer: "B) Well",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Present Continuous Tense indicates an action that is going on at the present time. For example, 'They are praying in the temple. He is revising his __________.'",
          optionA: "A) Breakfast",
          optionB: "B) Lesson",
          optionC: "C) Vacation plans",
          correctAnswer: "B) Lesson",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Past Continuous Tense is used to indicate an action that continued over a period of time in the past. 'The mechanic was setting his tools in order. They were thanking us __________.'",
          optionA: "A) Sincerely",
          optionB: "B) Gratefully",
          optionC: "C) Rudely",
          correctAnswer: "B) Gratefully",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Future Perfect Tense is used to indicate an action that will be finished by a certain time in the future. 'You will have milked the cow __________.'",
          optionA: "A) Every morning",
          optionB: "B) By 6 o'clock",
          optionC: "C) Before sunset",
          correctAnswer: "B) By 6 o'clock",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Present Perfect Continuous Tense indicates an action that began in the past and is still continuing. 'You have been studying in the same class for the last two years. She has been preparing for the competition since __________.'",
          optionA: "A) Yesterday",
          optionB: "B) Last month",
          optionC: "C) Last year",
          correctAnswer: "C) Last year",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Past Perfect Continuous Tense indicates an action that continued in the past until another action overtook it. 'She had been cooking dinner when she decided to invite me __________.'",
          optionA: "A) For it",
          optionB: "B) Tomorrow",
          optionC: "C) Next week",
          correctAnswer: "A) For it",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Future Perfect Continuous Tense indicates a continuous action that will take place in the future. 'They will have been planning for this house for __________.'",
          optionA: "A) Two years",
          optionB: "B) Next month",
          optionC: "C) Five days",
          correctAnswer: "A) Two years",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Present Perfect Tense is a combination of the past and the present. It indicates an action that took place in the past but has its impact in the present or is still relevant. 'The sun has risen in the __________.'",
          optionA: "A) North",
          optionB: "B) West",
          optionC: "C) East",
          correctAnswer: "C) East",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In the Simple Future or Future Indefinite Tense, 'This tense refers to an action that will take place in the future. For instance, 'I shall clean the room __________.'",
          optionA: "A) Now",
          optionB: "B) Later",
          optionC: "C) Well",
          correctAnswer: "B) Later",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };
}

if (localStorage.getItem("activityNumber") == 3)
  activityData = {
    activity: "Write 'True' for True and 'False' for False statements:",
    questions: [
      [
        {
          question:
            "The Simple Present or Present Indefinite Tense is used to express habitual actions or general truths.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Present Continuous Tense can indicate changes, trends, or developments over a period of time.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Past Continuous Tense is used to indicate an action that will take place in the future.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Present Perfect Tense indicates an action that took place in the past but has its impact in the present or is still relevant.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Future Perfect Continuous Tense indicates a continuous action that will take place in the future.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "In a Conditional Clause, the fulfillment of a hypothetical condition depends on the fulfillment of a real condition.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Subordinate Clauses are independent and do not rely on other clauses for their meaning.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Perfect Tenses are formed by combining past participles with the appropriate auxiliary verbs.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "True",
        },
        {
          question:
            "Present Perfect Continuous Tense indicates an action that has just completed.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
        {
          question:
            "The Simple Future or Future Indefinite Tense can only express actions that will occur in the distant future.",
          optionA: "True",
          optionB: "False",
          correctAnswer: "False",
        },
      ],
    ],
  };

export var activityData;
